{
  "grammar": {
    "src": ["./grammar/irregular-verbs.webp"]
  },
  "sentences": [
    {
      "question": "Становиться",
      "answer": "become became become",
      "tasks": ["become", "became", "become"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Приносить",
      "answer": "bring brought brought",
      "tasks": ["bring", "brought", "brought"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Выбирать покупку",
      "answer": "choose chose chosen",
      "tasks": ["choose", "chose", "chosen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Стоить",
      "answer": "cost cost cost",
      "tasks": ["cost", "cost", "cost"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Резать бумагу",
      "answer": "cut cut cut",
      "tasks": ["cut", "cut", "cut"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Мечтать",
      "answer": "dream dreamt dreamt",
      "tasks": ["dream", "dreamt", "dreamt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Пить",
      "answer": "drink drank drunk",
      "tasks": ["drink", "drank", "drunk"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Падать",
      "answer": "fall fell fallen",
      "tasks": ["fall", "fell", "fallen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Чувствовать",
      "answer": "feel felt felt",
      "tasks": ["feel", "felt", "felt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Расти капусту",
      "answer": "grow grew grown",
      "tasks": ["grow", "grew", "grown"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Слышать",
      "answer": "hear heard heard",
      "tasks": ["hear", "heard", "heard"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Ударять ногой",
      "answer": "hit hit hit",
      "tasks": ["hit", "hit", "hit"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Хранить секрет",
      "answer": "keep kept kept",
      "tasks": ["keep", "kept", "kept"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Знать о нем",
      "answer": "know knew known",
      "tasks": ["know", "knew", "known"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Класть что-то на стол",
      "answer": "lay laid laid",
      "tasks": ["lay", "laid", "laid"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Учиться",
      "answer": "learn learnt learnt",
      "tasks": ["learn", "learnt", "learnt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Покидть страну",
      "answer": "leave left left",
      "tasks": ["leave", "left", "left"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Одалживать деньги",
      "answer": "lend lent lent",
      "tasks": ["lend", "lent", "lent"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Позволять что-то делать",
      "answer": "let let let",
      "tasks": ["let", "let", "let"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Терять",
      "answer": "lose lost lost",
      "tasks": ["lose", "lost", "lost"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Звонить",
      "answer": "ring rang rung",
      "tasks": ["ring", "rang", "rung"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Продавать",
      "answer": "sell sold sold",
      "tasks": ["sell", "sold", "sold"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Закрывать",
      "answer": "shut shut shut",
      "tasks": ["shut", "shut", "shut"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Петь",
      "answer": "sing sang sung",
      "tasks": ["sing", "sang", "sung"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Спать",
      "answer": "sleep slept slept",
      "tasks": ["sleep", "slept", "slept"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Тратить деньги",
      "answer": "spend spent spent",
      "tasks": ["spend", "spent", "spent"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Стоять",
      "answer": "stand stood stood",
      "tasks": ["stand", "stood", "stood"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Воровать",
      "answer": "steal stole stolen",
      "tasks": ["steal", "stole", "stolen"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Плавать",
      "answer": "swim swam swum",
      "tasks": ["swim", "swam", "swum"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Учить",
      "answer": "teach taught taught",
      "tasks": ["teach", "taught", "taught"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Думать",
      "answer": "think thought thought",
      "tasks": ["think", "thought", "thought"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Бросать мусор в корзину",
      "answer": "throw threw thrown",
      "tasks": ["throw", "threw", "thrown"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Понимать",
      "answer": "understand understood understood",
      "tasks": ["understand", "understood", "understood"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Просыпаться",
      "answer": "wake woke woken",
      "tasks": ["wake", "woke", "woken"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Носить трусы",
      "answer": "wear wore worn",
      "tasks": ["wear", "wore", "worn"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Выигрывать",
      "answer": "win won won",
      "tasks": ["win", "won", "won"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Писать письмо",
      "answer": "write wrote written",
      "tasks": ["write", "wrote", "written"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Трясти, встряхивать",
      "answer": "shake shook shaken",
      "tasks": ["shake", "shook", "shaken"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Вести за собой",
      "answer": "lead led led",
      "tasks": ["lead", "led", "led"]
    }
  ]
}
